<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coding on Hugo Themes</title>
    <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/categories/coding/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coding on Hugo Themes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>Copyright © 2008–2019, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/categories/coding/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Color Spaces in OpenCV</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/opencv-color-spaces/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/opencv-color-spaces/</guid>
      <description>Image Segmentation Using Color Spaces in OpenCV + Python
In this article, you will learn how to simply segment an object from an image based on color in Python using OpenCV. A popular computer vision library written in C/C++ with bindings for Python, OpenCV provides easy ways of manipulating color spaces.
While you don’t need to be already familiar with OpenCV or the other helper packages used in this article, it is assumed that you have at least a basic understanding of coding in Python.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Started With the Slack API</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/slackapi/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/slackapi/</guid>
      <description>However, Slack wouldn’t be that useful if it was just a glorified AOL Instant Messenger. It’s the programmatic access to retrieve and send messages with the Slack web application programming interface (API) where the power really kicks in.
In this post, we’ll see how to work with Slack via the API and the official SlackClient Python helper library. We will grab an API access token and write some Python code to list, retrieve and send data through the API.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Flask Create News Web Application</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/example/flask_news_web/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/example/flask_news_web/</guid>
      <description>Python Flask Create News Web Application by Parwiz
In this Python Flask article iam going to show you how to Create News Web Application, basically we are using News API website for getting our API Key. so simply you can open News API website after that create a New Account and get your API Key, for more information you can check the video for this article in the below.
Also you can check How To Build News Web Application In Django</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python vs JavaScript for Pythonistas</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/pythonistas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 19 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/pythonistas/</guid>
      <description>If you’ve never used JavaScript before or have felt overwhelmed by the quick pace of its evolution in recent years, then this article will set you on the right path. You should already know the basics of Python to benefit fully from the comparisons made between the two languages.
In this article, you’ll learn how to:
 Compare Python vs JavaScript Choose the right language for the job Write a shell script in JavaScript Generate dynamic content on a web page Take advantage of the JavaScript ecosystem Avoid common pitfalls in JavaScript  Free Bonus: 5 Thoughts On Python Mastery, a free course for Python developers that shows you the roadmap and the mindset you&amp;rsquo;ll need to take your Python skills to the next level.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Python Flask Create News Web Application</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/flask_news_web/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/flask_news_web/</guid>
      <description>by Parwiz
In this Python Flask article iam going to show you how to Create News Web Application, basically we are using News API website for getting our API Key. so simply you can open News API website after that create a New Account and get your API Key, for more information you can check the video for this article in the below.
Also you can check How To Build News Web Application In Django</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Python Standard Library By Example</title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/pythonstandardlibrary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/pythonstandardlibrary/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;PyMOTW-3 is a series of articles written by &lt;a href=&#34;http://doughellmann.com/&#34;&gt;Doug Hellmann&lt;/a&gt; to demonstrate how to use the modules of the &lt;a href=&#34;http://www.python.org/&#34;&gt;Python&lt;/a&gt; 3 standard library. It is based on the original &lt;a href=&#34;http://pymotw.com/2/&#34;&gt;PyMOTW&lt;/a&gt; series, which covered Python 2.7. See &lt;a href=&#34;https://pymotw.com/3/about.html&#34;&gt;About Python Module of the Week&lt;/a&gt; for details including the version of Python and tools used.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>โมดูล (Module) </title>
      <link>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/modules/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://knowledge-dragons.github.io/KM/articles/post/modules/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;โมดูล (Module) คือไฟล์หรือส่วนของโปรแกรมที่ใช้สำหรับกำหนดตัวแปร ฟังก์ชัน หรือคลาสโดยแบ่งย่อยอีกหน่วยหนึ่งจากโปรแกรมหลัก และในโมดูลยังสามารถประกอบไปด้วย คำสั่งประมวลผลการทำงานได้&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
